chinesepod.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy

(Last revised on May 30, 2018)

This policy (the "Policy") provides a general statement of the ways in which CHINESEPOD LIMITED ("CHINESEPOD" or the "Company") collects and processes personal data received from you on our website, through social media or otherwise in connection with our business. Please read this Policy carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal data.

Despite being domiciled outside the jurisdiction of the European Union, we voluntarily adhere to Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 (the "Recommendation") on the protection of natural persons with regards to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, known as General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), as a welcome guidance of sound business practices. Such adherence is on a goodwill basis only and the Company may, at its sole discretion, make changes to this policy at any point in the future that may or may not comply with the Recommendation.

Our website address is:  

Our Company Name is:  
ChinesePod Limited

Our registered address is:  
246 West Broadway  
New York NY 10013  
Unites States of America

You can contact us at +1-212-666-8000 or [support@chinesepod.com](mailto:support@chinesepod.com) for any issue related to the processing of your personal data.

CHINESEPOD may have been provided with contact or personal information by an individual or corporation or CHINESEPOD may have obtained contact or personal information about an individual or corporation in the ordinary course of business. Obtaining this information is important to CHINESEPOD's ability to deliver information and provide services, but the Company also recognizes that such individuals or corporations expect their information to be treated appropriately.

The Sources of Information: The personal information collected by the Company comes primarily from information provided by individuals through CHINESEPOD's Website, contact information provided in the ordinary course of CHINESEPOD's business and information gained from social media and public sources by CHINESEPOD.

The Type of Information: The typical information CHINESEPOD collects about the Company's contacts includes name, title, company or TV Channel name, address, phone number, email address, and possibly other information.

Use of Personal Information: CHINESEPOD may use personal information to administer, operate, facilitate and manage an individual's relationship with the Company. This may include sharing such information internally, as well as disclosing it to third parties under limited circumstances. CHINESEPOD may contact an individual by mail, telephone, electronic mail, fax, etc., in connection with such individual's relationship with the Company, or to provide an individual with news about CHINESEPOD, broadcast exhibition invitations, case studies, new product features or other information that is believed to be of interest. CHINESEPOD may use personal information to facilitate the Company's internal business operations, fulfilling CHINESEPOD's legal and regulatory requirements, including document retention and the requirement to provide information to regulatory authorities upon request.

Disclosures of Personal Information to Third Parties: CHINESEPOD does not disclose personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that: (a) perform software development or other services in connection with projects involving CHINESEPOD, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to CHINESEPOD; and (b) sponsor or manage trade shows, conferences or events where CHINESEPOD is a participant. CHINESEPOD may also disclose personal information to fulfill an individual or corporation's instructions, to protect the Company's rights and interests and those of the Company's business partners, or pursuant to an individual's express consent. Finally, under limited circumstances, personal information may be disclosed to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations, for instance, when responding to a subpoena or similar legal process, to protect against fraud, and to otherwise cooperate with law enforcement or regulatory authorities.

Sale of Personal Information: CHINESEPOD does not sell personal information to third parties.

Access to or Modification of Personal Information: An individual is entitled to access any personal data about that person held by CHINESEPOD by sending a written request to the individual identified below. A valid means of identification may be required as a security precaution to assist the Company in preventing the unauthorized disclosure of personal information. CHINESEPOD will process the request within the time provided by applicable law. An individual is also entitled to have CHINESEPOD modify or delete any information that is believed to be incorrect or out of date.

Contacting CHINESEPOD: If an individual does not wish to be contacted by CHINESEPOD, if an individual wishes to exercise rights of correction and access, or if an individual requires further information regarding CHINESEPOD's privacy policies please contact our legal counsel at:

Jonathan Morton, Esq.  
Morton & Associates LLP  
246 West Broadway, New York NY 10013  
United States

212-796-4300 phone
